Finding Aid for Announcements, Bulletins, Handbooks (University of Michigan), 1883-ongoing
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Announcements, Bulletins, Handbooks (Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies) 1883-ongoing
Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies
3.5 linear feet
0578 Fimu C164
Graduate School of the University of Michigan. Includes Bulletins and Anouncements of courses and degree requirements, graudate student hand books and other infomration for graudate students.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Publications from Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies (Donor no. 972 ) are received periodically.
The record group is open without restriction.
For history, see the finding aid for Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies records.
The Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies Announcements, Bulletins and Handbooks series consists of publications directly related to graduate school policies and procedures and includes information on degree program requirements and curriculum. The core titles included in the series are Announcement/Bulletin, Graduate Student Handbook and Information for Graduate Students. Some publications (or their successors) may no longer be available in print but are available on the school s website.
Note: Other publications produced under the auspices of the Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies, such as Rackham Reports, are separately cataloged.
Subjects:
University of Michigan--Graduate work.; University of Michigan--Curricula--Periodicals.; Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies.
Genre Terms:
CD-roms
- Announcements, Bulletins, Handbooks
  - Announcement
    (includes Program Degree Requirements)
    - 1883-1887 (Box 1)
    - 1892-1910, 3 volumes (Box 1)
    - 1916-1957/58, 18 folders (Box 2)
    - 1958/59-1961/62, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Bulletin
    - 1962/63-1985/86, 14 folders (Box 3)
    - 1986/87-2004/05, 10 folders and one CD-ROM (Box 4)
  - Doctoral Student Handbook, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Graduate Student Handbook
    - 1981-1998, 7 folders (Box 4)
  - The Graduate Handbook, published by Rackham Student Government, 1969-1978 (Box 4)
  - Information for Graduate Students (includes application form)
    - 1965-1991/92, 16 folders (Box 4)
- Archived Rackham Graduate School Website
  The Rackham School of Graduate Studies Archived Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the Rackham School of Graduate Studies. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the School. The website series is arranged chronologically, with captures from 2002 and 2003 stored on CD. Starting in 2010, this archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/.
  - Website capture, May 15, 2002, 1 cd (Box 2)
  - Website capture, June 22, 2003, 1 cd (Box 3)
  - Archived Horace H. Rackham School of Graduate Studies home page, 2010-[ongoing]
  - Archived websites related to the Rackham School of Graduate Studies, 2010-[ongoing]